So, as usual.
じゃあ、いつもの感じで
I always take my top off.
いつも上から脱ぐんだ
That's good, I like the style.
いいっすね、スタイルいいね
Thin!
細っ!
Are you eating rice?
ご飯食べてる?
Shall we go?
いきます?
That's amazing, it can reach your back.
すごいね、背中届くんだ
I can't reach it.
俺届かない
Oh, really?
え、本当に?
That's amazing, I'm about to receive it now.
すごいね、今めっちゃ届いちゃう
Why haven't I received it?
なんで届かないの?
No, I don't know.
いや、分かんない
Aren't women softer?
女性の方が柔らかくない?
The body.
体は
Thick.
太 い
Wow, that's thick.
すごい、太い
You're tall, aren't you?
身長高いよね
185cm?
what?
何?
100 How old is it?
100いくつだっけ?
170cm?
How many centimeters?
何センチ?
160cm
It was really cold.
め っちゃ冷た
Well, let's go in.
じゃあ、入りましょうか
Thank you very much for your hard work.
どうもお疲れ様です
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
is.
です
Well, I'd like to ask you a few questions.
じゃあ、ちょっと質問をしていきたいんですけど
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何ですか?
Udon.
うどん
Ah, I like udon.
あ、 うどん好きなんだ
fruit?
果物?
What about food?
食べ物は?
What is not a fruit?
果物じゃないやつは?
Udon.
うどん
Ah, I like udon.
あ、うどん好きなんですね
What udon?
何うどん?
Ordinary udon.
普通のうどん
No udon?
うどんもない?
Ordinary.
普通の
So, is mentai kodon no good?
じゃあ、めんたいこうどんとかダメですか?
good.
良い
So, what food do you dislike?
じゃあ、嫌いな食べ物は?
celery.
セロリ
So, is that the green one?
で、あの緑色のやつだっけ?
celery?
セロリ?
That bitter one?
あの、苦いやつ?
Celery?
セロリか
I'm a little confused about celery and parsley.
セロリとパセリがちょっと混乱してるんだけど
What is celery?
セロリって何だっけ?
Um, is that it?
あの、あれか
Something like green onions.
長ねぎみたいなやつか
Oh, I hate that.
あー、あれ嫌いなんだ
Eh, why?
えー、なんで?
Because it's bad.
まずいから
bad?
まずい?
Because it's bad?
まずいから?
What else do you dislike?
他に嫌いな物は?
strawberry.
いちご
Oh, you don't like strawberries?
えー、いちご嫌いなの?
Eh, why?
えー、なんで?
Because it's bad.
まずいから
Isn't it bad?
まずくなくない?
bad.
まずい
Which one is sweet?
甘いやつは?
bad.
まずい
Ah, but it's bad.
あ、でもまずい
Ah, strawberry is no good.
あ、いちごダメなんですね
Isn't it an allergy?
アレルギーとかじゃなくて?
bad.
まずい
Is it bad because it's bad?
まずいからダメ?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
So when did you do Edge for the first time?
じゃあ、初めてエッジいつしました?
In life.
人生で
How old are you?
何歳?
Probably around 15.
多分、15くらい
Oh, 15 years old?
あ、15歳?
Oh, Senpai?
おー、先輩?
different.
違う
Did you lose?
損失した?
It will probably be a loss.
損ないるし、多分
How many points?
多 分?
Tame's house?
ため の家?
Did you do it at a special house?
ための家でやったの?
You have parents, right?
親いるでしょ、だって
If I was 15 years old, if it was for a reason.
15歳だったら、ためだったら
when?
何時?
Around what time?
何時くらいに?
Oh, I don't know.
あ、わかんない
night?
夜?
Isn't it night?
夜じゃない?
Ah, evening.
あ、夕方
Oh, before my parents came home?
あー、親が帰ってくる前とか?
Ah, is that so?
あー、そういうことか
Ah, I kind of like you, that's it.
あー、ちょっと好きがあるね、それね
Did it hurt?
痛かった?
Did you bleed?
血出た?
It wasn't out.
出てなかった
Isn't it coming out?
出てないの?
That's rare.
珍しいっすね
I usually make chudim.
普通、チューディム作るね
So it was my first time, but I was told it wasn't my first time.
だから、初めてだったんだけど、 初めてじゃないって言われた
Oh, so you were suspected?
あー、疑われたってこと?
Ah, that's a common thing.
あー、よくあるやつだ
surely.
確かに
Maybe so.
そうかもね
What, were you exercising?
え、運動してた?
何個?
I haven't.
してない
Oh, so isn't there a track and field club?
あ、そうなんで、陸上部とかじゃない?
It was an art club.
美術部だった
Ah, if you were a track and field athlete,
あー、陸上の選手とかやってたら、
It seems that Macs can be damaged by exercise machines.
マックが、 運動機に破けるらしいですけどね
So, which body do you like?
じゃあ、好きな体は?
Normal bit.
正常位
Oh, missionary position?
あ、正常位?
What about the back?
バックは?
dislike.
嫌い
Do you hate Mac?
マック嫌いなの?
マック嫌いなんだ?
Did you hate Mac?
マック嫌いだったの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
why?
なんで?
it hurts?
痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
Ah, it hurts deep inside.
あー、奥までが痛い
But is it okay if you are kind?
でも、優しかったら大丈夫?
dislike.
嫌い
Do you dislike it?
嫌いなの?
Do you hate it that much?
そんなに嫌いなの?
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほど
So, is missionary position better?
じゃあ、正常位がいいの?
Yeah.
うん
So, shall we go?
じゃあ、行きますか?
hot.
熱い
hot?
熱い?
Ah, let's go out.
あー、出よう
Hey, let me see your Mac.
ちょっと、一旦マック見せて
Ah, fluffy.
あ、ふわ
Very pink mac.
めっちゃピンクマック
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?